Hello there.
I'm Josue. I'm
a web
designer and developer
from New Zealand.
I work freelance.
I jump
into agencies and
help them out
or work directly
with, my own
clients as well.
I'm making a
new series called
Webdune Diaries. Webdune
is the trading
name of
the business
I work under.
it's just me.
It's nothing fancy.
Webdune Diaries is
all about what
goes on behind
the scenes. I
feel like when
I started, there
wasn't many people,
talking transparently about
the difficulties
of being a
freelancer, especially in
the web world.
so I wanted
to, wanna
start a
series talking about
that sort of
stuff, get things
off my chest.
Problem shared is
a problem halved,
so you know,
taxes and GST
and upcoming bills
and those
moments of,
feast and famine.
That happens
a lot with
freelancing, those famine
moments are tough,
like so many
times I wanted
to just fully,
quit. So it'll
be interesting to
talk more about
that sort of
stuff and then
also talk about
the stuff I've
learned along the
way. My notes
are over here.
it says season
one, this is
gonna be broken
down into seasons,
just to keep
like a
goal per
season, keep some
sort of continuity.
the first season
is about me
wanting to build
a website for
Fox Stevenson. He's
a favourite, music
artist of mine.
I'd love to
upgrade his website
big time, and
bring way more
personality to it.
The last talking
point is, I
don't wanna keep
this too long,
tomorrow's episode,
I'm gonna
try to do
them daily, tomorrow's
is about where
I'm actually at,
what's going on
in my business.
yeah, see
you tomorrow.